杰
Jay?
你看到葡萄了没
Have you seen the grapes?
-我吃完了  -你为什么把葡萄吃了
- Yeah, I ate them. - Why would you eat the grapes?
因为它们放在碗里  洗过了
They were in a bowl, they were washed,
而且是我花钱买的
I paid for them.
那是为新年准备的
They were for the new year's.
对了  要用它们做什么蠢事来着
Oh, right. What's that goofy thing again?
才不蠢呢  那是一种传统
It's not goofy. It's a tradition.
你在午夜时分吃下12颗葡萄
At midnight, you eat 12 grapes,
许下12个心愿  新年的每个月一个
you make 12 wishes, 1 for each month of the year.
你还真相信吗
And you really think that works?
五年前
Five years ago,
我是一名住在贫民窟里的单亲妈妈
I was a single mother living in a slum.
如今  我就要开着新车
Today, I'm driving to Palm Springs
和我的大款老公一起去棕榈泉了
in my new car with my rich husband.
随你怎么样  反正我要吃葡萄
You do what you want. I'm eating the grapes.
除夕之夜  我们会带着菲尔和克莱尔
For new year's eve, we're taking Phil and Claire
以及米奇尔和小卡去棕榈泉一家
and Mitch and Cam to this amazing hotel
我曾住过的一家超棒的酒店玩
I used to go to in Palm Springs.
他们那儿提供全套的服务
They got a whole package--
晚餐  舞蹈和午夜祝酒
Dinner, dancing, toast at midnight.
我想问  夫复何求啊
I mean, what more do you need?
-葡萄  -我说过我们会在路上停一下的
- Grapes. - I said we'd stop on the way.
海莉  今天是除夕夜
Haley, it's new year's eve.
你确定你不想参加个派对什么的
Are you sure you don't wanna go to a party or something?
然后听我所有的朋友唠叨
And listen to all my friends talk about
大学生活有多赞吗
how awesome college is?
我知道大学生活有多赞
I know how awesome college is.
那正是我被踢出来的原因
That's what got me kicked out.
我相信米奇尔舅舅
Well, I'm sure uncle Mitchell
要是知道有你在家坐镇的话
will feel much better leaving Lily here
一定会更乐意把莉莉留在我们家的
knowing that you're in charge.
你知道其实是你管事  对吧
You know you're really in charge, right?
你们怎么就知道我不用参加派对呢
How do you know I don't have a party?
好吧  当我没问
Okay, fine.
莉莉  你准备好和表哥表姐们一起住了吗
Lily, are you ready for your big sleepover with your cousins?
谁照看我啊
Who's watching me?
-海莉  -我说真的
- Haley. - I'm serious.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
好的  我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
每年的除夕夜  都是
Every new year's eve, it's like,
"我们干点啥  我们干点啥"
"What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?"
所以我们对杰策划的活动很满意
So we were happy that Jay planned this whole thing.
那真的是  免去了我们为了
It really, you know, takes the pressure off
超越自己而承受的压力
of having to outdo ourselves.
是啊  叫我们如何胜过去年呢
Yeah, and how are we gonna possibly top last year?
我们睡过头了吗
Oh. Did we miss it?
才十点钟
It's only 10:00.
-什么  -才十点钟
- What? - It's only 10:00.
这地方比我印象里小了点
Place is smaller than I remember.
你就觉得小而已吗
Smaller's your issue?
杰  你上次来这里是什么时候
When was the last time that you were here, Jay?
没多久  74年75年左右
Not that long ago. 1974, '75.
是我两岁的时候吗
So when I was 2?
你这么说我就不乐意了
I don't like when you do that.
我看过他们的网站  照片看起来挺漂亮的
I checked the web site. The pictures looked beautiful.
妈呀  蜥蜴
Oh! Lizard. Huh?
永远别相信网上的照片
Never trust pictures on the internet.
只要找好拍照的角度
Shoot it from the right angle,
你可以让所有东西显得更大更好
You can make anything look bigger and better.
他说的是房子  死变态  他是房产经纪人
Houses, you pervs. He's a realtor.
我就觉得听到动静了
I thought I heard voices.
罗比  我跟你说嘛  来人了
Robby! I told you! It's people.
我的天呐  那就是20年后的我啊
Oh, my god. That's me in 20 years!
好吧  你要是她  我就是抛弃她的人
Okay, you be her, and I'll be whoever left her.
我们办入住  预订名字是普里契特
Uh, we're checking in. It's under Pritchett.
杰·普里契特  三间房
Jay pritchett. Three rooms.
你以前在我们这里住过
You've been with us before.
那个本子用了多少年了
How old is that book?
这里有些什么东西黏黏糊糊的
Oh, there is something sticky over here.
罗比
Robby!
那东西回来了
It came back.
不可能啊
It's not possible.
好吧  这个地方确实大不如前了
Okay, so the place is not what it used to be.
不过我们还是会玩得开心的
But we're gonna have fun.
在星光照耀的房间里用餐
Dining in the starlight room,
在谢莉·斯特罗曼三重奏下翩翩起舞
little dancing with the Shelley Stroman trio.
三人组只剩两人了  给你钥匙
Oh, there's just two left. Here are your keys.
退房时间是11点  要是你想待久一点
Check out's at 11:00, but if you wanna stay longer--
11点没问题
11:00 is good.
就是这里了
Here we go.
有什么问题吗
Is there anything wrong?
没有没有  我们只是希望
No, no. No, we were just hoping for something
-更有浪漫气氛  -拜托
- a little more romantic. - Come on, now.
没有那么糟糕
It's not that bad.
-那里面有什么  -没什么
- What's in there? - Nothing.
要是你想找浪漫的地方
If you're looking for romance,
附近有一处很隐蔽的温泉
there's a secluded hot spring nearby.
-就像一块璞玉  -是吗
- Kind of a hidden gem. - Huh?
只要顺着高尔夫球场
Just follow the path
12号洞右边的小路走就能找到
right by the 12th hole of the golf course.
听起来很不错啊
That sounds kinda nice.
隐蔽的  天然的
Secluded. Natural.
-性感的  -性感的
- Sexy. - Sexy.
你觉得怎么样  菲尔
What do you think, phil?
温泉有没有鸡蛋味儿啊
Does it smell like eggs?
有些温泉跟鸡蛋一个味儿
Some of them smell like eggs.
我和菲尔已经好久没有...
It's been a while since Phil and I...
十二月份整个月
The whole month of December?
都没有一次...
Not even a...
或者是打快...你懂的
Or a quick... you know?
说起来挺难为情  那不是我们的作风
It's embarrassing, and it's not like us.
让我觉得很紧张
That's making me anxious,
所以我才会真的需要...
Which is why I really need to get...
再次感谢
Thanks again.
对  那是给你的
Yeah, that's yours to keep.
好了
Okay.
再见了
Bye now.
我建议我们不和我爸吃晚餐了
I say we bag dinner with my dad,
去找那个温泉吧
and go find that hot spring.
亲爱的  我们不能丢下你爸
Honey, we can't just ditch your father.
他希望我们全家人一起
He wanted us all to be together.
我们一直在一起
We are always together.
我的天  难道我们还指望
Oh, my god, what are we gonna hear
听到什么新鲜事吗
that we've never heard before?
米奇尔和小卡那个关于莉莉如何用
Mitch and Cam's inspiring story
海姆立克急救法救下小孩的动人故事吗
of how lily saved that kid with the Heimlich?
拜托  不就是她抱他一下
Please. She hugged him,
他就把口香糖吐出来了嘛
and he spit his gum out.
不如我们拿上一瓶香槟
I say we get a bottle of champagne,
仰望着星空
Look up at the stars,
不穿游泳衣
forget our bathing suits.
听起来确实诱人
That does sound hot.
不过到时我只会一心想着你爸的
But I'd just be thinking about your dad the whole time.
我去冲个澡
I'm gonna hop in the shower.
里面有什么
What's in there?
没什么
Nothing.
太好了  不  是好极了
Oh, perfect. No, great.
要是我们需要袜子的话
If we need any socks,
床上正好有人留了一只
someone left one in the bed.
我的神呐  克里斯宾去灯塔
Oh, my gosh. There is no way Crispin stays here
是绝不会住在这里的
when he comes to the Beacon.
什么灯塔
What's the beacon?
就是他经常大加赞赏的那个俱乐部啊
The club that he's always raving about.
就在那条街边上
It's right down the street.
那才是我们该去的地方
That's where we should go.
迎新年找乐子的地方
Somewhere fun for new year's,
趁着我们还算年...轻吧
while we're still young... ish.
我们翘掉晚饭去那里吧
L-let's get out of dinner and go there.
-怎么翘  -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
有了  有了
Um... okay, okay.
你可以在餐桌上假装病了
Um, y-you could pretend to get sick at the table.
假装咳嗽  胃疼
You know, fake a cough, stomachache,
随你选  我无所谓
dealer's choice. I don't care.
装得像一点  好让我们离开
Just sell it and get us out of there.
可是你爸怎么办
But what about your dad?
他想让全家人聚在一起
He wants the family to be together.
我们总在一起
We are always together.
我们都听克莱尔讲了无数次
I mean, how many times do we have to hear Claire tell us
卢克对儿科医生的搞笑反驳了
Luke's hilarious comeback to the pediatrician?
天啊  我们真应该叫她"矮平房"
Oh, gosh. We should start calling her "Ranch house"...
因为她没有第二层[第二个故事]
Because she doesn't have a second story.
-不错嘛  -我知道  谢谢
- So good. - I know! Thank you.
你确定不跟我们一起玩
Hey. You sure you don't wanna play
"饥饿游戏"吗
"The hunger games" with all of us?
我的人生就是一出饥饿游戏
My whole life is a hunger game.
不然你以为我为什么对你这么刻薄
Why do you think I'm so mean to you?
找我的
That's for me!
进来吧
Hey. Come on in.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
嘿  我出局了
Hey, I'm out.
这是贝卡和她的表姐乔伊丝
This is Becca and her cousin Joyce.
乔伊丝是你的
And Joyce is for you.
什么  我有约会吗
What? I'm on a date?
可我还没喷古龙水
But I'm not wearing any cologne.
你之前知道这事吗
Did you know this was happening?
我现在也不知道这怎么回事
I don't even know what this is.
乔伊丝  这是曼尼
Joyce, this is Manny.
初次见面  甚感荣幸
Pleasure to make your acquaintance.
不知小姐是否有意来杯气泡果酒呢
Can I offer you a glass of sparkling cider?
他可不是你说的那样
He's not how you described him.
别担心  你会爱他的
Uh, don't worry. You'll love him.
曼尼  说点浪漫的
Manny, say something romantic.
我没法突然打开浪漫模式  你来说些浪漫的
I can't just turn it on. You say something romantic.
衣服不错
Cool shirt.
我能参观你房间吗
Can I see your room?
专门为你打扫了
Well, I didn't clean it for me.
他们单独上楼了
They're going upstairs alone.
-那是不允许的吧  -我不知道
- Is that even allowed? - I don't know.
-我们是不是得说点什么  -比如
- Should we say something? - Like what?
比如  "这是不可以的哦"
Like, "It's not okay"?
应该是吧  是吗
Well, maybe it is. Is it?
我不知道  我只是感觉
I don't know. I just feel like
我们没有尽到保姆的职责
we're not doing our job as babysitters.
我们当然尽到了
Of course we are.
我好冷  我还看到了一只郊狼
I'm cold, and I saw a coyote.
然后卢克对他说
And Luke turns to him and says,
布劳斯坦医生  不是吧  晚餐都不吃就想这样
"Dr. Blaustein, really? Not even dinner first?"
对天发誓  布劳斯坦医生亲口讲的
Hand to god! Dr. B. Told me himself!
我挺抱歉的  但我爱这个地方
You know, I'm sorry, but I love this place.
我知道这里有点糟糕
I know it's a little rough around the edges,
但我总是在这玩得很开心
but I've always had a good time here,
今晚感觉特别好
and I'm having a great time tonight.
是呀
Yeah.
你的俄式炸鸡怎么样
How's your chicken kiev?
-真心不错  -很好吃
- It's really good. - It's very good.
-好吃  -对  仿佛身临俄国
- Tasty. - Yeah, tastes like Russia.
你还等什么  快说不舒服
What are you waiting for? Get sick.
还没到时候  该说的时候我会说的
Not yet. I'll know when it's time.
亲爱的
Honey.
-你睡着了  -是嘛
- You were sleeping. - I was.
真是不好意思  克莱尔
Ay, I'm so sorry, Claire.
绝不是因为你把卢克
It wasn't because you were telling again
和那个医生的故事又讲了一遍
The luke and the doctor story.
只是我最近太累了
It's just that I've been so tired lately.
天啊
Oh. Oh, gosh.
你还好吧  她这一天都感觉不舒服
Are you okay? She's been feeling bad all day.
对  我想我可能是染上什么小病了
Yeah, you know. I think I might be coming down with a little something.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
就是啊  我之前用她的杯子喝水了
I know. I drank out of her glass earlier.
-不是  她用了我们的借口  -什么
- No. She's stealing our excuse. - What?
亲爱的
Honey.
歌洛莉亚  醒醒
Wake up, Gloria!
淡定  如果留下掌印  我要遭白眼了
Easy. If that makes a mark, I get the stink eye.
我送你上楼去
I'm gonna walk her upstairs.
你需要躺会儿了
I think you need to lie down.
好吧  就小睡一会养足精神再玩儿
Okay. Just a little disco nap.
那我们走了  今晚很开心
Okay. Well, this has been fun.
别别别别别  别动
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
继续狂欢  我会尽快回来
Keep the party going. I'll be back as soon as I can.
不是吧  现在
There it is. Now?
不是  我有东西卡喉咙了
No, I have something stuck in my throat.
真遗憾没有莉莉在这里给你做海姆利克急救
It's too bad Lily's not here to give you the heimlich.
我们跟你们说过那个故事没
Did we ever tell you guys that story?
你要说吗
Do you wanna tell it?
-恩  让我说  -好吧
- Yeah, let me tell it. - Okay.
杰  你应该回去和你的家人在一起
Jay, you should go back and spend time with your family.
我不能在除夕夜把你一个人丢下
I can't leave you alone on new year's eve,
尽管所有人都在等我快回去
even though everyone's waiting for me to come back.
真是贴心呀
Aw, that's so sweet.
我只是希望我
Yeah. I just hope I don't hold up
不会错过火焰樱桃
the lighting of the cherries jubilee.
杰  如果你真的想去  你就...
Jay, if you really want to go and--
好的
Okay.
大家去哪了
Where'd everybody go?
我不知道  他们应该都走了
I don't know. I guess they all left.
你还要火焰樱桃吗
You still want the cherries jubilee?
点燃吧
Light 'er up.
嘿  这不是杰·普朗奇特吗
Hey, if it isn't Jay Plunkett.
不是  是杰·普里契特
It isn't. It's--it's Jay Pritchett.
新年过得怎样
You having a good new year's?
够扫兴的  大家都放我鸽子
Eh, kind of a bust. Everybody bailed on me.
我要睡觉了
I'm gonna hit the sack.
我们刚被一个人放了鸽子
Hey, we just had a guy who bailed on us.
你玩德州扑克吗
You play hold'em?
玩啊  但我应该...
Yeah, but I should probably, uh...
玩多大的
What's the buy-in?
杰
Jay...
打个招呼吧  马丁  老虫
Say hello to, uh, Marty, Bugs...
嘿  你好啊  杰
Hey. How ya doin', Jay?
-我的前夫雨果  -好啊
- My ex-husband hugo... - Hey, how you doing?
-还有比利·迪  -嘿
- And Billy Dee. - Hey.
不是开玩笑吧  比利·迪·威廉姆斯
Are you serious? Billy Dee Williams?
我是你的超级粉丝啊
I'm a huge fan.
那你得呆在这了
Well, now you have to stay,
因为这些人在《桃花心木》后
since none of these guys have seen me
就没在电影里见过我
in anything since "Mahogany."
-那片我也没看过  -我也是
- Never even saw that. - Me either.
你们开玩笑呢
You're kidding.
比利·迪扮演一名市议员
Billy Dee's an alderman
设法让戴安娜·罗斯待在芝加哥
trying to keep Diana Ross in Chicago,
而不是成为
rather than become
一名国际模特和设计师
an international model and designer.
我儿子逼我和他一起看的
My son made me watch it with him.
他是基佬
He's gay.
很好  我可不想由我来告诉你这事
Oh, good. I didn't want to be the one to tell you.
抱歉  先生  打扰一下
Excuse me! Sir, excuse me!
他是故意的
He's doing this on purpose!
他可能只是没注意到我们
He probably just doesn't notice us.
他怎么可能没看到我们
How can he not notice us?
我们是这里仅有的穿了袖子的
We're the only people in here in sleeves!
嘿  你想要什么
Hey there. What can I get for ya?
抱歉  年轻人  我先来的
Excuse me, young man. I was here first.
年轻人  你为什么不叫他毛头小子
Young man? Why don't you just call him whipper-snapper?
这也太荒谬了  我们竟然连酒都喝不到
This is ridiculous. We can't even get a drink.
这里都是11岁的  而且我好热[性感]
Everyone in here's 11, and I'm hot!
如果我们够性感  现在就不会没酒喝了
If we were hot, we'd be drinking right now.
如果我们乖乖待在餐厅
Yeah, and if we'd stayed put,
现在就可以享受火焰樱桃了
We'd be enjoying cherries jubilee right now!
别这样  小卡  拜托
Hey, hey, hey. Cam, come on.
今天是除夕夜  我们一起出来玩啊
It's new year's eve. We're out together.
喜欢跳舞的开心果小卡哪里去了
Where's fun cam who likes to dance?
这里
Here.
他  他去哪了
Wh--where--where is he?
-我在这里  -他在这里
- I'm over here. - Oh, there he is!
-来嘛  -好吧  不好意思啦
- Come on! - Okay, I'm sorry.
我刚只是觉得被无视了  会好起来的
I was just feeling invisible! It'll get better!
好吧  这是湿的  我受够了
Okay, you know what? That is wet. I'm done.
老天啊  不要啊  别啊
oh! God! God, no!
他们在里面好久了
They've been in there forever.
做点什么啊  你是管事的
Do something. You're in charge.
得了吧  我们都知道我是有名无实的
Oh, please. We both know I'm just a figurehead here.
你真认为他们在里面做什么吗  他才12岁
You really think they're doing something in there? He's 12.
他14了  但你们这么亲密真感人啊
He's 14, but it's touching how close you are.
好吧
Fine.
你们干什么
what do you want?
你得把门开着
You have to keep your door open.
-为什么  -你为什么要关上门
- Why? - Uh, well, why do you need it closed?
因为我们正要亲热呢
Because we're gonna make out.
你...
Well, you...
你不能关着门
You can't have your door closed.
为什么  你们想观摩还是怎么着
Why? Do you wanna to watch or something?
那有点变态啊
That's weird.
我们才不想看呢
Of course we don't wanna watch.
那就好
Perfect.
-但你不能...  -你这是...
- But you can't... - What are you d...
什么情况
What just happened?
要来一杯迪尔加多酒吗
Can I offer you a Pinja Delgado?
是我自创的调酒
It's my own concoction.
里面有什么
What's in it?
这么说吧  这酒清爽  甜美
Let's just say it's cool, it's sweet,
还富有奇思妙想
and it's not afraid to embrace its own whimsy.
我不是那个意思
I'm not saying that.
我也不会喝的
I'm not drinking it, either.
那...新年你有什么新决心吗
So... You making any resolutions?
有  绝不再和不认识的人约会
Yeah. No more blind dates.
你好刻薄
You're mean.
她说得对  乔伊丝  你真刻薄
You know, she's right, Joyce. You are mean.
我如此热情地款待你
I've been a gracious host
你却这么无礼  坏脾气  又无聊
while you've been rude, sullen, and dull.
失陪了  抱歉我不想让我的新年
You'll forgive me if I choose not to start the new year
以如此消极的方式展开
on such a negative note.
对了  你一会儿要是想吃西兰花
Oh, and if you're hungry for broccoli later,
可以去你的牙缝里找一块儿
you'll find a piece in your teeth.
那该死的小路在哪儿啊
Where is this stupid path?
我们走了好久了
We've been walking forever.
会找到的
We'll find it.
你有没有觉得那个服务生不太对劲
Did that bellman seem a little off to you?
没错  没准这里根本没有温泉
Oh, totally. Maybe there is no hot spring.
没准这是密谋杀害我们的计划中的一步
Maybe this is all part of an elaborate plan to kill us.
你干嘛吓唬我
Why would you even say that?
我只是活跃一下气氛
I'm just trying to lighten the mood.
你情绪很紧绷
You seem so tense.
放松  这是在探险  有趣的探险
Come on. This is an adventure. This is fun.
我不想探什么险
I don't wanna have an adventure.
我不需要有趣的探险  我想和你滚床单
I don't wanna have fun. I wanna have sex with you.
什  什么
Wha--what?
别让我重复
Don't make me say it again.
不  我想听你再说一遍
No, I want you to say it again.
这次最好能叫出我的名字
Maybe throw my name in there this time.
克莱尔  你怎么了
Claire, what's going on?
你知道我们有一个月没滚过了吗
Do you know that it's been a month?
-没那么久  -有  一整个月
- No, it hasn't. - Yes, it has.
上次还是感恩节后那天
Day after Thanksgiving.
我记忆犹新  因为那天我在预算内
I remember because I came in under budget
买到了所有要买的圣诞礼物
on all of my Christmas gifts,
你知道这种事多么让我兴奋
And you know how that gets me going.
-没错  -是啊
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
我还开玩笑说你衣冠不整
I made that joke about your clothes being half-off.
但我们还是滚了床单
And yet we still did it,
因为以前我们就是那么干柴烈火
'cause that's the kind of people we used to be.
现在这是怎么了
What happened?
没怎么  我们一直很忙
Nothing happened. We're busy.
节日嘛  再加上迪迪又来了
It was the holidays. Dede was here.
你知道她总是让我
You know, she has a way of...
性欲全无
shutting that whole thing down.
但我们现在成了那样的夫妻吗
But is this who we are now?
先是一个月不滚床单  接着就是一年
I mean, first it's a month, then it's a year,
然后我们开始各睡各床
Then we're sleeping in twin beds
你会叫我"老妈"
and you're calling me "mother".
我无法忍受
And I can't even bear it,
因为我们成了我祖父母
'cause we're just like my grandp--
我们去找到那个温泉
Let's go find that hot spring
然后以温泉中的激情一夜
And start this new year off with...
开启我们新的一年
sex in a hot spring.
好了  好了
All right, all right.
我们接下来要做什么
Where--where should we try next?
-我嚷了吗  我嚷了  -是的
- Am I yelling? I'm yelling. - Yes.
也许我们应该去买些冻酸奶吃
Yeah. Maybe we should just go get some frozen yogurt
然后回房间睡觉
And call it a night.
别  小卡  来嘛
No, Cam, come on.
我们不能再一次在除夕夜
We can't have another New Year's eve
撑不到午夜就睡觉
where we don't even make it to midnight.
我...节日的一切
I... This entire holiday
都在提醒着我  岁月流逝
is just a giant reminder of how the clock is ticking.
每过一秒
You know, each passing second
我们就离死亡更进一步
is just bringing us that much closer to death.
至于吗你  就因为我提出吃冻酸奶
All this because I suggested some fro-yo?
我...我好讨厌变老的感觉
I'm... I'm sick of feeling old.
我真的想狂欢一下
I-I really need this.
好吧
Okay.
让我们狂欢到午夜
Let's get you to midnight.
好
'kay.
看  他和我们年纪差不多
Oh, look, he's our age.
他去的地方  一定也适合我们
Wherever he's going, I'm sure he'll fit right in.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  我不予评判
Okay, no judgment.
这种生活方式完全没问题
Perfectly acceptable lifestyle.
-只是不适合我们  -没错
- Just not for us. - No!
但我们不会就这么放弃的  对吗
Okay, but we are not giving up, all right?
我们就像《三只熊的故事》里的金发小妞
We're like goldilocks.
[童话故事  讲述一个金发少女闯入了三只熊的领地]
刚刚第一家酒吧太幼齿
The first bar was too young,
第二家又...不管第二家那是什么
The second was... Whatever that was,
第三家一定就完美了
And the third will be just right.
米奇尔
Mitchell...
[同性恋圈中对壮硕多毛的男人的称谓]
三只熊
Three bears.
我没说错吧
I mean... Right?
这里  就是这家
Here. This one.
你不是想感受年轻吗
You wanted to feel young.
此刻宛若少男
And I do.
对不起  我总是拒人千里之外
I'm sorry. I push people away.
我知道自己有这毛病  但就是改不了
I feel myself do it, but I can't stop.
你连自己都不喜欢  很难喜欢上别人
It's hard to like someone when you don't like yourself.
你说得对
You're right.
你有那么多优点
You have so many good qualities.
魅力四射  聪明伶俐  活泼阳光
You're attractive, you're witty, you're bright.
真希望你能看到我眼中的你
I just wish you could see yourself through my eyes.
你真是个好朋友
Aw, you're such a good friend.
朋友  闹半天只是朋友吗
Friend? That's where this is headed?
友谊地久天长嘛
Well... Friendships last longer.
这段可不行  我朋友够多了
Not this one. I've got enough friends.
祝你新年快乐  乔伊丝
Happy New Year, Joyce.
海莉  你打算怎么办
So what's the plan, Haley?
我得进去  那里面可是我们的亲弟弟
I'm going in. That's our baby brother up there.
我还没准备好接受这一切
I'm not ready for all of this.
女孩儿还有荷尔蒙什么的  太恶心了
The girls, the hormones-- it's gross.
我们不能就这么闯进去
Well, we can't just barge in.
上次闯进爸妈房间  那场景还在我脑中
I'm still trying to get the image of mom and dad
挥之不去...天呐  又浮现了
out of my... oh, god, it's back.
我进来啦
I'm coming in!
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
把洗好的衣服送过来
Just putting away some laundry.
那是个胸罩吧
That's a bra.
以及一块桌布
And a tablecloth.
你不能一会儿再来吗
Can't you do this later?
不好意思  你妈知道你在这里吗
Excuse me. Does your mother know you're here?
-知道  -她知道我们家长不在家吗
- Yes. - Does she know our parents aren't?
知道
Yeah.
停顿太长  没有目光接触
Big pause, no eye contact.
姐撒谎的本事可比你强多了
I was so much better at this than you.
-你得走了  -不  她不能走
- You're out. - No, she's not.
不  她得走  很晚了  你才13岁
Yes, she is. It's late, you're 13...
-14岁  -才14岁
- 14. - 14,
除非这位妮可·贱奇
and unless Nicole Bitchie here
想让我打给她家长  揭发她撒了谎
wants me to call her parents and tell them she lied...
我得走了  再见  卢克
I better go. Bye, Luke.
等等  为什么她得走
Wait. Why does she have to go?
因为我让她走她就得走
Because I said so.
又不是你说了算
You're not the boss.
别跟你姐姐顶嘴
Don't talk back to your sister.
我恨你们
Ugh! I hate you!
你现在恨我  以后会感激我的
You hate me now, but someday you'll thank me!
我想我欠妈妈一个大大的道歉
I think I owe mom a huge apology.
还有没有人管我了
Is anyone watching me?
对A加对8
Aces and eights.
天妒红颜  我有三张J[同名电影]
Lady Sings the Blues. Three Jacks.
对不住了  比利·迪
Sorry, Billy Dee,
哈利王子在赌城全裸
But where do you go to tattle on prince Harry
你要向谁告状啊
when he's naked in vegas?
Q的顺子[直接找女王告状]
Straight to the queen.
好了  我不玩了
Well, that's it. I'm out.
我也是
Me, too.
见鬼  差不多11点了
Oh, hell, it's almost 11:00.
我得去星光室了
I gotta do my set in the starlight room,
我已经错过肉馅饼了
and I'm missing a pasty.
大家这是怎么了  还早呢
Oh, what's the matter with everybody? It's early yet.
就是  我到这里后
Yeah, I'm having fun
第一次感觉到开心
for the first time since I got here.
杰
Jay?
她来多久了
How long has she been there?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria...
大家都放我鸽子
Everybody ditched me,
这些人邀请我玩扑克
these guys invited me to play poker,
瞧瞧我旁边坐的是谁
and look who I'm sitting next to.
她太年轻不会知道的
Oh, she has no idea.
你好  我是比利·迪·威廉姆斯
Hello, I'm Billy Dee Williams.
你好  我是她老婆歌洛莉亚
Hello. I'm Gloria dee wife.
杰  差不多午夜了  我们忘了买葡萄
Jay, it's almost midnight, and we forgot to buy my grapes.
有叫客房服务吗  说不定有葡萄
Did you try room service? They probably have grapes.
就没新鲜的
Oh, nothing fresh.
但总是可以从什锦水果罐头中捞到
But you can always fish some out of a can of fruit cocktail.
杰  你知道我需要真正的葡萄来许愿
Jay, you know that I need real grapes for my wishes.
那是哥伦比亚传统  只是适度的疯癫而已
It's a Colombian tradition. It's only moderately insane.
我家有葡萄
Well, I have grapes at my house.
不  我可不想搅黄你的新年安排
No, I don't want you to blow new year's.
拜托  每晚对比利·迪来说都是除夕夜
Oh, please. Every night is new year's for Billy Dee.
我喜欢你  比利·迪
I like you, Billy Dee.
到了午夜  就吃葡萄许愿
So at midnight, you eat them and then you make your wishes.
听起来有些印象
Well, that sounds vaguely familiar.
我可能在和夏洛
I might have heard about that
拍《爱船》的时候听说过
when I did that "Love boat" with Charo.
你认识夏洛吗
You know Charo?
他可迷恋夏洛了
He's so obsessed with Charo.
不是吧
No kidding.
我的天
Oh, my god.
经典劳斯莱斯险路车
A classic rolls corniche.
我这辈子都超迷这款车
I have been in love with this car my whole life.
在我的村子里  如果你没开这种车
In my village, if you didn't drive one of these,
你都不好意思叫自己是毒品大王
you couldn't call yourself a drug lord.
你想开吗
Would you like to drive it?
那不是明知故问吗
Does the bear sit in the woods?
典型的夏洛
Classic Charo.
那么
So...
我的崩溃值得吗
Was it worth my meltdown?
总是值得
It always is.
只有我们两个  在沙漠的夜空下
Just you and me, under the desert sky.
我是沙漠枭雄[电影名]
I'm Lawrence of Arabia,
你是
You're Mrs...
枭雄的太太
Of arabia.
你们好啊
Hey there.
我的妈呀
Oh, my god.
太好了  你们是最先到的
Sweet. You're the first ones here.
欢迎
Welcome.
欢迎来到哪里
Uh, welcome to what?
来到"除衣夜"  有看到宣传单吗
To nude year's eve. You saw the flyer?
没有
No.
我告诉他们的
I told them.
罗比
Robby.
我  哇  "除衣夜"
So I--whoa. Nude year's eve?
-你说的原来是"除衣夜"  -真有才的近音词
- You said nude year's eve. - It's clever.
对  我们是棕榈泉裸体协会的
Yeah. We're the palm springs nudist association.
这是我们庆祝新年的方式
It's how we celebrate the new year.
-我看出来了  -清新的感觉  犹如初生婴儿
- I can see. - Fresh. Like newborns.
裸着
Naked.
对  我看出来了
Yeah. I got that.
我的天  我们得离开这里
Oh, my god. We have to get out of here.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
我们的衣服被压下那堆下面
Our clothes are trapped under that pile.
你真想裸着站起来
You really wanna stand there naked
在那堆裤子中翻来翻去吗
sifting through all those drawstring pants?
-好吧  挪挪  -挪过去
- Okay. Scooting over. - Just... Just scootch in.
-好的  -挪过去
- Okay. - Scootin'.
菲尔  有东西碰到我了
Phil, something just touched me,
不是你身上的
And it's not from your side.
谁要香槟
Who wants champagne?
我要
Oh, I'll have some.
好吧  我的天
Okay. Oh, my gosh. Okay.
对不起  抱歉我太过去了
Oh, sorry. Pardon the reach.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们得赶紧开溜
We gotta make a run for it.
现在走太失礼了
Well, now it's just gonna seem rude.
菲尔
Phil.
我太爱这辆车了
I love this car so much!
你接下来要带我们去哪里  比利·迪
Where you gonna take us next, Billy Dee?
你会看到令你眼前一亮的惊喜
A surprise that's gonna blow your mind.
叫我比利就行了
And just call me Billy.
才不干呢
Not doin' it.
这是那边一桌的先生们送的
And these are from the gentlemen at that table over there.
免费酒水  免费酒水又来了
Oh, free drinks. More free drinks.
谢谢  谢...他们听不到
Thank you. Thank--they can't hear me.
谢谢
Thank you!
这肯定就是模特的感觉
This is what models must feel like.
打扰下  有没有人跟你说过
Excuse me, but has anyone ever told you
你就是年轻版的范·强森[演员]
you look like a young Van Johnson?
没人说过  不过你真会说话
Oh, no. That-- that's so sweet, though.
多谢
Thank you.
他给你"免费入场券"呢
Free pass?
在你手机上找出范·强森的照片
Pull up Van Johnson on your phone.
我需要知道是该欢喜还是该担忧
I need to know how I feel about that.
他可帅了  你就高兴吧
He was gorgeous. You're fine.
这样可真爽  被人夸  有人请喝酒
This is nice, huh? Compliments, free drinks.
还有什么比这更爽的
What could be better?
好了  先生们  差不多午夜了
Alright gentlemen! Almost midnight!
嘴巴嘟起来吧
Pucker up.
新年真奇怪
New Year's is so weird,
会让你想到时光流逝
the way it makes you think about time.
十  九  八
Ten... Nine... Eight...
小卡
Cam.
我想正是这样
I think that's why
人们才给自己巨大压力  要在新年玩得开心
people put so much pressure on themselves to have fun.
七  六  五
seven... six... five...
我想我大概明白了
I mean, I guess I sorta get it.
四  三  二  一
four... three... two... one!
快点  许愿吧
Quick, quick! Make your wishes!
就像现在  我只希望能让时间放慢脚步
Like right now I wish I could just slow down time,
因为我完全没有准备好他长大成人
'cause I am so not ready for him to grow up yet.
我懂
I know.
我希望他永远是我们的笨弟弟
I want him to stay our stupid little brother.
新年快乐
Hey, happy new year.
你也快乐
You too.
我的天  这里面放了什么
Oh, my god, what is in this?
抱歉  那杯是我的
Oh. Sorry. That one's mine.
我发誓  我太紧张了
And I swear to you, I was so nervous,
我想我穿上了别人的内裤
I think I might have put on somebody else's underwear.
我是说真的
I'm not kidding.
我爱死这故事了
I love this story.
-几乎和你的一样棒  范·强森  -妈呀
- Almost as good as yours, Van Johnson. - Oh, my god!
看  杰来了
Oh, look. Here comes Jay.
我好内疚  他错过了所有的精彩
I feel bad he missed all this fun.
-爸  -瞧他们回来了  我忠诚的家人
- Hi, dad. - Look, they're back. My devoted family.
各位  这是我们亲爱的朋友  比利·迪·威廉姆斯
Everyone, this is our dear friend, Billy Dee Williams.
天啊  《星球大战》里的蓝多
Oh, my god, it's Lando.
恕我冒昧  威廉姆斯先生
Excuse me, Mr. Williams,
我得告诉你
I just have to tell you,
我从小就好爱你
I've loved you since I was a little boy.
我现在真是"求星大战"
I'm so Starstruck right now.
你一定是米奇尔吧
Well, you must be Mitchell.
你的事杰都告诉我了
Jay told me all about you.